jigoshop.com 2019-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Jigoshop

This privacy page explains what information this website collects in order to provide services to: Visitors to our website (s) People who use our services, such as newsletter subscriptions or purchasing themes and plugins. Users of our support forums and Premium Membership Options

## **Website visitors**

When someone visits Jigoshop.com we collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behavior patterns, which is collected in a way which does not identify anyone, and we do not associate any data gathered with any personally identifying information from any source. Any personal information collected will be clearly marked and will explain our purpose in collecting it.   **We do not store credit card** **details nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties**

## **Cookies used by Jigoshop.com**

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.  
**Google Analytics**   (_utma, _utmb, _utmc, _utmv, _utmz). Cookies which collect anonymous data about how visitors use our site. Visit [this link](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)[ ](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)for more information.  
**WordPress session cookies** : (PHPSESSID) These are required to enable WordPress to function.  
**Youtube cookies** : We embed Youtube videos from our own and other channels which may set cookies once you click on the Youtube video player. Visit [this link ](http://www.google.com/support/youtube/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&answer=171780)for more information.

## **Email newsletter subscriptions**

Personal information supplied as part of the sign-up process to subscribe to the Jigoshop weekly email newsletter will only be used to provide the requested email communications and will be stored by Campaign Monitor, our email service provider.

## **Purchase information**

Personal data supplied during the purchase process will be used by our payment providers (Paypal) to facilitate payment. This includes Support packages, which will also store user data to enable access to our support forums and services.
